<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>活动汇总 | 通用人工智能实验班</title>
    <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>活动汇总</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>zh-Hans</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://tongclass.ac.cn/media/icon_hu444d86ff9c8bc6b3e6f8c2a3492878e5_142951_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>活动汇总</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Experience Sharing Around AI Research and Pursuing a Doctor&#39;s Degree</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-04-01-sat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-04-01-sat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/thu-tong-saturday-afternoon-talks/1.ResearchAndPhD/Poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poster&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;speakers&#34;&gt;Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siyuan Huang is a Research Scientist and Team Lead at Beijing Institute for General Artificial Intelligence (BIGAI) and teach at Peking University. He graduated from Tsinghua University with a Bachelors in Department of Automation and received his Ph.D. from Department of Statistics at University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) advised by Professor Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in computer vision, machine learning, cognition and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baoxiong Jia is a Ph.D. candidate of Department of Computer Science, University of California, Los Angeles, currently working at VCLA@UCLA advised by Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. He received his B.S. in Computer Science from EECS, Peking University in 2018 and obtained his M.S. in Computer Science at UCLA in 2019 under the supervision of Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in the intersection of computer vision, artificial intelligence and cognitive science.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Assembly of TongClass</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-tong-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-tong-event/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/tongclass-meeting/1.2023-03-25/Agenda.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Agenda&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for a Research Career with Confidence and Enthusiasm</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-04-sat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-04-sat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/thu-tong-saturday-afternoon-talks/1.ResearchTips/Poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poster&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;speakers&#34;&gt;Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liangru Xiang is a first year Ph.D candidate from the Department of Automation, Tsinghua University, under the supervision of Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. He looks forward to making the agents as smart as humans do. His research interests lie in causal learning and reasoning, cognition, machine learning and other topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Puhao Li is a Senior student from the Department of Automation, Tsinghua University. He has just received the pre-admission to a PhD program at Tsinghua University, to be advised by Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in computer vision, generative modeling and robotic manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Essential Guide on Using GPU Computing Servers</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2022-11-25-tfn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2022-11-25-tfn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Computing servers play a crucial role in AI research, but it is struggling for many researchers to master how to use them. We attribute most problems to their lack of basic skills in using the servers and their ignorance of how the system works. This talk provides a thorough and hands-on guide on essential techniques for using GPU computing servers. It goes through skills from using SSH for logging, to using Conda and Docker for more flexible environment management. To help our audience understand better, we provide adequate but easy-to-understand explanations of technical details. Audiences can have a chance to practice the skills on a new Tong Class server and have a Q&amp;amp;A session, for which on-site participation is suggested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/thu-tong-friday-night/1.ComputingServers/Poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poster&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;speaker&#34;&gt;Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuyang Li is a member of the Technology and Network Committee of the Tsinghua Tong Class, and the technical lead of Tong Class 2020. He is responsible for managing the GPU servers and maintaining the official website for THU Tong Class. He has worked in Linux system ops for more than five years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tong Paper Saturday E01 - Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2022-04-09-vit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2022-04-09-vit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;speaker&#34;&gt;Speaker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yu Liu is the leader of the class of 2020. His research interests include object-centric learning and machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
