<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research | 通用人工智能实验班</title>
    <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/tag/research/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://tongclass.ac.cn/tag/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>research</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>zh-Hans</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://tongclass.ac.cn/media/icon_hu444d86ff9c8bc6b3e6f8c2a3492878e5_142951_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/tag/research/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Persuit of a Research Career with Confidence and Enthusiasm</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-04-01-sat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-04-01-sat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/thu-tong-saturday-afternoon-talks/2.ResearchPursuit/Poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poster&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;speakers&#34;&gt;Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siyuan Huang is a Research Scientist and Team Lead at Beijing Institute for General Artificial Intelligence (BIGAI) and teach at Peking University. He graduated from Tsinghua University with a Bachelors in Department of Automation and received his Ph.D. from Department of Statistics at University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) advised by Professor Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in computer vision, machine learning, cognition and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baoxiong Jia is a Ph.D. candidate of Department of Computer Science, University of California, Los Angeles, currently working at VCLA@UCLA advised by Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. He received his B.S. in Computer Science from EECS, Peking University in 2018 and obtained his M.S. in Computer Science at UCLA in 2019 under the supervision of Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in the intersection of computer vision, artificial intelligence and cognitive science.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for a Research Career with Confidence and Enthusiasm</title>
      <link>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-04-sat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tongclass.ac.cn/event/2023-03-04-sat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://assets.tongclass.ac.cn/events/thu-tong-saturday-afternoon-talks/1.ResearchTips/Poster.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poster&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;speakers&#34;&gt;Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liangru Xiang is a first year Ph.D candidate from the Department of Automation, Tsinghua University, under the supervision of Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. He looks forward to making the agents as smart as humans do. His research interests lie in causal learning and reasoning, cognition, machine learning and other topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Puhao Li is a Senior student from the Department of Automation, Tsinghua University. He has just received the pre-admission to a PhD program at Tsinghua University, to be advised by Prof. Song-Chun Zhu. His research interests lie in computer vision, generative modeling and robotic manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
